Jordan Bryant

Art Director & Digital Product Designer

597 N Holliston Ave Pasadena, CA 91106 (323) 540-7703 jsbrymail@gmail.com jordanbryant.design

ABOUT ME

Over the last 8+ years I've worked with companies including A24, AT&T, Cablevision, Directv, Lionsgate, Microsoft, Mitsubishi, Sony, Southern California Edison, Universal, and Warner Bros. creating immersive digital experiences that delight and have a positive and lasting impact.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Los Angeles, CA - Art Director / Designer

SEP 2016 - PRESENT

- Art direction and digital product design for a variety of clients.
- Video production and motion design.
- Mentorship of junior to mid-level designers.

Concept Arts, Hollywood, CA - Digital Art Director

MAR 2015 - SEP 2016

• Art direction and design of various digital and social campaigns.

Directv, El Segundo, CA - Ul Designer

JUN 2014 - MAR 2015

UI Design of various Directv/AT&T products.

Possible, Culver City, CA - Designer

DEC 2013 - MAY 2014

- UI design for Cablevision's Optimum app.
- Design of digital marketing content for Mitsubishi Motors.

Schematic, Culver City, CA - Associate Designer

NOV 2011 - DEC 2013

• Creation and management of style guides for developer handoff.

EDUCATION

California State University, Northridge - BA, Graphic Design